<root>
            <description>ICE.com via Buy.com offers this 1-Carat T.C.W. Black &amp; White Diamond Sterling Silver Bracelet for $115 with free shipping. That's the lowest total price we've seen for this bracelet by $45. It features black and white diamonds set in a sterling silver tennis bracelet.</description>
            <description>Sony Style offers the Sony VAIO Core i7 1.6GHz 16.4" Widescreen Notebook in Black or Gray, model no. VPCF1190X, for $999.99. With free shipping, that's the least expensive quad-core Sony VAIO laptop we've seen. Sales tax is added where applicable. Features include an Intel Core i7-720QM 1.6GHz quad-core processor, 16.4" 1600x900 widescreen LCD, 4GB RAM, 320GB 5400 rpm hard drive, DVD burner, NVIDIA GeForce 310M 512MB video card, Gigabit Ethernet, 802.11n wireless, Bluetooth 2.1+EDR, webcam, Windows 7 Home Premium 64-bit, and more.</description>
            <description> HandHeldItems.com offers this Translucent Shell Case with Screen Protector for Apple iPod touch in seven colors (Clear Black pictured) for $7.99. Coupon code "TOUCHBACKSHELL" drops it to $2.99. Add $2.85 for shipping. That's tied with our November mention and it's the lowest total price we could find by $7. It features PVC construction, cutouts for all buttons, and a screen protector. It's compatible with 2nd- and 3rd-generation iPod touch MP3 players. Coupon expires January 31.</description>
            <description> Dell Small Business offers the Iomega eGo II 500GB USB 2.0 Portable Hard Drive in Blue, model no. 34747, for $99.99 with free shipping ($0.20/GB). That's $20 off and the lowest total price we could find for this model. It's also tied for the lowest total price we've seen for an eGo drive of this capacity. Sales tax is added where applicable. This "Designed for Dell" drive features a Power Grip Band and Drop Guard Xtreme feature to protect it from data damage if it falls.</description>
            <description> Amazon.com offers the Dockers Boys' 8-20 Short Sleeve Pique Polo in Red (pictured), White, Light Blue, or Navy for $9.99. Shipping adds $4.98, or get free shipping on orders over $25. Even with shipping, it's the lowest total price we could find by $12. It's available in sizes S to XL, although not all size/color combinations are available.</description>
            <description> Sears offers the DieHard Universal Power Adapter for $9.97. Shipping adds $6.95, or opt for in-store pickup. Even with shipping, that's $20 off and tied with our December mention as the lowest total price we could find. Sales tax is added where applicable. This adapter features 12 connectors and an adjustable output voltage.</description>
            <description> Dickies offers the Dickies Women's Eisenhower Jacket in Black (pictured) or Navy for $15.99. Add $7 for shipping. Although that's $8 over our December mention, since expired, it's still the lowest total price we could find by $19. This jacket is lined in quilted nylon taffeta. It's available in sizes S through XXL, though some color/size combinations are sold out.

Update: It's since fallen to $9.50 in sizes S to L, and $10.25 for XL and XXL.</description>
            <description> Subway offers downloads of The Biggest Loser and Subway Workout Mix for free. It's the best deal we've seen for such an album. This 12-track album features workout remixes of songs from Lady GaGa, Taylor Swift, Rihanna, and more.</description>
            <description> Macy's offers the Tommy Hilfiger Men's Inverse 3-in-1 Coat in Woodchuck (pictured) or Navy for $36.99 plus $9.95 for shipping. That's $162 off list and the lowest total price we could find for this jacket. Sales tax is added where applicable. It's available in navy in sizes S to XXL and woodchuck in size XXL only. Deal ends January 9.</description>
            <description> eForCity.com via Buy.com offers this Premium Multi-Function Cradle for Blackberry Pearl 8100 for $9.56 plus $2.98 for shipping. That's a buck under what eForCity.com charges directly and it's the lowest total price we could find for such a cradle. It serves as a stand while charging via its USB connection.</description>
            <description> PC Micro Store knocks 50% off its entire selection of cell phone accessories via coupon code "Dealnews50%Cell". Plus, bag free shipping on most items. In all, thousands of items are available for models from Apple, LG, Nokia, Motorola, and more. (Scroll down to see them all.)

A best bet is the PCMS Apple iPhone 3G Snap-On Case with Screen Protector (pictured) for $6.97 after discount. Coupon expires after 200 redemptions.</description>
</root>